PROPHECY TIME
Hallelujah.
The brother under the canopy - your wife is at home but you are here with a lady.
What kind of prayer you want to offer?
What do you hear us preaching since morning?
Your wife is at home. She is even trying to cook food for you but you are here with one lady.
For salvation or for what?
For marriage.
If you don't come out, you are here to tempt me.
If you tempt the man of God, you know the repercussion. You have to come out, please.
Salvation first.
You will not be able to help yourself.
God loves you. Thank you.
Hallelujah.
This man comes forward in response to the prophecy of the man of God.
Man of God, I am the man who came here with my girlfriend while my wife is at home.
What has your wife done to you?
She didn't do anything.
And she's beautiful - you like her?
Yes.
It is urge.
I came with the girl. The girl is my girlfriend in Angola.
Where is the girl?
She is at the back.
No, respect others. This is the man I called.
After the service, I want to see you and her.
Okay? I want to see her because you are the cause.
We are going to ask God the way out.
Thank you, my brother.
PROPHECY CONFIRMATION
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Kelechukwu John.
The woman beside me is my wife, Chioma John.
I'm the one the man of God prophesied about last Sunday that I came with my girlfriend.
It started in Angola.
When I newly got there, I met her and she said that she would help me and give me documents.
That's why we started.
Whenever she came to my house, we would like to watch Emmanuel TV.
She said that she liked the man of God and would one day like to visit Nigeria.
Two Fridays ago, she called me saying that she was in Cotonou,
that I should come and pick her up.
I went to pick her up and brought her to The SCOAN
and the man of God gave us a prophecy.
After the prophecy, I realised my mistakes.
I'm sorry, Man of God, for doing such a thing.
I am also pleading for my wife to forgive me because she did not know anything about it.
My wife trusted me and did not think that I would do such a thing.
Man of God, I am sorry; forgive me for what I did.
She asked me about my wife and I told her that the man of God had invited my wife.
She said that she could not stand the challenge and went back.
So your girlfriend has actually left now after hearing that the man of God was inviting your wife?
She left.
Right now as your wife is here, what do you want to say to your wife?
All I want to say is that she should forgive me for what I did. I'm sorry, baby.
We thank God. Our brother said that after the word of prophecy, he realised his mistake.
That it was as if his eyes opened.
We thank God Almighty for how that word of prophecy not only brought our sister here
but also brought deliverance to our brother who was having a girlfriend all the way in Angola.
Let's just hear a word from our sister.
Madam, you're welcome. Just introduce yourself to us.
Emmanuel!
(God With Us - Matthew 1:23)
My name is Chioma Kelechukwu.
I am from Nigeria.
On Tuesday, I got a call that the man of God and Emmanuel TV team wanted to see me.
I came and they explained what was happening.
I was surprised and did not know what to do.
I trusted my husband and did not think that he could do such a thing.
Nevertheless, to God be the glory, I got my deliverance at The SCOAN.
I thank God and Emmanuel TV for helping me recover my home.
Thank you.
Amen. Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We give glory to the Lord God Almighty that this prophecy came forth.
As you are standing here right now in the presence of God, madam, what do you want to say to your husband?
I have forgiven him!
Thank You, Jesus Christ. Let's put our hands together for Jesus!
I advise every home to know God first so that God will help you recover your family.
Thank you.
Mr & Mrs Kelechukwu John
(Prophecy Confirmation)
Hallelujah. Once again, madam, for the benefit of our viewers,
as you're standing here in the presence of God now, what do you want to say to your husband?
Who am I? I have already forgiven him.
Let's put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
Glory be to God. We know that if not for God's intervention,
an issue like this could have easily led to many things - talk of divorce, separation or whatever.
But we thank God that as God revealed it, He also redeemed this marriage,
and we thank Jesus Christ for what He has done.
We want to hear a final word from our brother as well.
My advice to every couple is that there is no need to look outside -
stay with your wife, place your hope in her and do everything with her.
Amen. Let us put our hands together for Jesus Christ!
We thank God for your life, sir,
and we pray that God will give you the grace to maintain this resolution you've made right now.
As you here in the presence of God, we know your past is over
and we believe you and your wife will come back with a wonderful testimony, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Mr & Mrs Kelechukwu John
(Prophecy Confirmation)
We believe you have been inspired by the clip you have just watched.
Click here to subscribe to witness more of God's power at work in our generation today,
and stay up-to-date with the latest prophecies, deliverances,
sermons and testimonies from The SCOAN.
Emmanuel TV - Changing Lives, Changing Nations and Changing the World.